Guys, what's up?  It's great to
see you all again, or rather, it's great that you see me again
.
Just a quick note, the video will continue shortly
.  I just want to get you all
excited for Kalash, the
audio drama will be released soon in about
a month, and at the end of this video
I'd like to show you a short
sample.  It's simply an
amazing feeling when the German
Diicabri voice reads from your book
.  And, uh, the thing is, it's
a radio play, not an audiobook.  That means
you can hear the footsteps, you can hear the bar,
you can hear the mufflers being installed,
you can hear the tires squealing.  It's like a version of
Terentin for blind people without
feet.  So, um, first of all, enjoy
the video.  See you soon.
Thank you.  What a reception!  It's
awesome, man.  It
sold out so quickly.  I am ashamed.  I am
ashamed.  [laughter]
No, really.  I am ashamed
because I always worry so much
about comments on the internet where
I think, "My career is over, that's it
."  Everyone hates me, I do
n't know either, people write
things, is that supposed to be funny?
And I always try
to remain polite and correct, and then I reply
and write: "Dear Hannelore,
you have two thumbs.
Just scroll down. Perhaps you'll find
an advertisement for a remedy
for your constipation further down."
But I don't always have that energy.
And then people write things like: "Your
humor is shallow and stupid."  I
[snort] say: "Yes, just like your mom."
At least my mom is funny.  Yes.  And it took
her nine months to come up with her biggest joke
.
And since I criticized the woke community
, I've also been receiving messages from
the front.  When news like this comes out, it means
men have become so toxic.  And I
say no, toxic masculinity has existed
since Adam and Eve.
When Adam suddenly realized I
had the biggest penis in the world,
I think there weren't any horses back then.
And then she texts me: "What's it
actually like having a penis? It
can be tough sometimes. [laughter]
Sometimes I have people in my
show who record me
with their phones and then upload the clip to
Instagram or TikTok
and call Nikita Miller
misogynistic, homophobic, racist.
I've never seen anything like it. Some
Silke with blue hair
who looks like she should be the
CEO of Thermomix.
[laughter] I
asked my grandpa where
all these things suddenly came from. Nikita, look
, we haven't burned any witches in over 300 years
. [laughter]
I always thought that's how
equality works. I dish it out in
all directions. Everyone has to get it
. And if I
leave someone out, that would be discrimination.
I think you don't get far in life
if you're constantly trying to be
politically correct. I've been telling
my sister that for years.
My sister has a T-shirt that says:
"I'm VOGE, I'm
vegan."  And I love gender-inclusive language."
Hey,
she got insulted, she got
spat on, she got kicked. And
she didn't even leave the house.
[laughter]
People keep threatening me that I'll get
canceled and something's going
wrong. I'm still here and I've
said everything.
I think to get canceled, I'd have to do
something crazy. I'd have to
grab a boy's ass or
something. But even then, there'll be a
backlash, with people
saying, "Wait a minute, what was that
boy even wearing?"
#freethepriests
and there will be a
counter-movement to that as well, a movement where
100 boys express themselves.  Yes,
he grabbed my ass too.
Yes, me too.  He walked through the
kindergarten like that.  [laughter]
And then people want a statement
from me.  They want me to show remorse
.  So I have to stay up for three nights straight to look desperate
.
And then I make a selfie video.
Yes, I don't even know what happened
.
Jonas, I thought we were friends.
I will withdraw for a while to
heal and reflect, and
I won't go on tour again before then.  Then
I see the statement from the tax office.
One week later I'm back on
tour.
At this point, people say: "Hey,
if you keep making
jokes like this, your career will soon be
over."  I say, "No,
because we live in a time where
we have a chancellor who's sleeping with a
pedophile president
. But now anything goes.
[applause]
Everyone's angry, everyone's so
charged up. Hey, I used to go
online to escape reality.
Now I go outside to
escape the internet.
Everyone's angry. It's war
. Man against woman. Women [ __ ] men
. Men [ __ ] women. It's getting worse
and more complicated.
I miss those times when everything
was so simple, so easy. Elementary school.
I see two eight-year-olds in the sandbox.
[clears throat] Can I play?
Only if you show us your dick.
[laughter]
Yeah, I'll show you my dick for a second and sit down
.
By the way, I was eight too. Don't get me
wrong. Okay,
[laughter]
but now, now, that's it,
and when I ask women, men do
n't have such a good connection to their
emotions. When I ask men, what's
the problem? Then these rare and
They're taking my schnitzel away.
Women have a much better connection
to their feelings. And when I
ask women, what's the problem?
They say, "Men are the problem,
men are dangerous."
And I say, okay, if that's true,
how come the
crime rate is so low on Mother's Day?
Because women are distracted.
[laughter]
10% of women take medication to
keep their mental state under control. That means
90% of women are still
walking around free. [laughter]
Still untreated. Don't
get me wrong. I'm a
fan of temperament. I love
women's boxing.
I love women's UFC. And people ask
me, "Hey, how can you watch that?"
And I say, "By just
imagining them fighting for me."
[laughter]
It broke my heart when
trans women were excluded from women's sports
. Oh, that hurt so much
. I still remember the
trans woman versus woman boxing match, and I
was like:  "Give me this, do it, and people
were like, 'Wow, you're so woke and
enlightened.'"  I say: "No, I
bet on her. [laughter]
Did you see her biceps?
K first round. I have to pay rent."   It's a
shame she didn't make a statement after the fight
.  Sentences like:
"I am a woman through and through, and if anyone does
n't like it, they can suck my penis
."
What I also often hear is
from women.  The problem is the
lack of appreciation for men.
Pregnancy alone.  Women
tell me that during pregnancy,
we go through hell.
Childbirth alone is a painful experience that
men simply cannot comprehend.  And
if they could, they would
die in the process.
Scientists have
discovered this.
Scientists, why do they want to
find that out?  Don't they have their
own problems?  [laughter]
I
can tell you, a kick in the nuts
is harder than any pregnancy.
I can explain it.
When a woman
has recovered from her pregnancy and
is fully regenerated,
she will say sometime months later: "I
want to be pregnant again."
[Laughter]
But no man in this world, no matter
how hard I kick his balls off
, [Laughter]
comes to me four months later and says:
"Hey, [Laughter]
that's something."
Now, the whole thing is a
bit unfair to those who
are unintentionally pregnant. And there, too,
I say, where's your initiative?
If men were capable of
being pregnant, we'd have
an abortion clinic
with a voucher at every rest stop. [Laughter]
[Applause]
And what I also hear very often, which
is also disturbing, is that men think they can do
everything better than us. I do
n't know.
But what I do know is what men are
definitely better at than women is
being a woman.
Bruce Jenner, Olympic champion,
the pinnacle of male evolution.
60 years later, he looks in the mirror
and thinks:
"Wrong body."
And then he has himself surgically altered to become
a woman. What's the technical term?
Decide, I think, right?
[Applause]
Now she's called Caitlyn Jenner.  Caitlyn
Jenner was named
Woman of the Year that same year, along with others.
Never had a period, never been
pregnant. Her salary was
n't cut either,
because it wasn't necessary. People
saw it and said, "Wow,
we've never seen anything so naturally feminine
."
Oh, I feel anger.
You have to keep that to yourselves, otherwise
you're transphobic.
I once asked my grandma, "Grandma, what
will you women be without us men?"
Fat and happy. [laughter]
The dating scene has
changed a lot too.
People use Tinder. Back then I thought,
cool, that's for shy people who do
n't leave the house, who don't
have time. No, that thing is for
slackers.
I saw it. People lie on
the couch, watch football, and
swipe left and right at the same time. That's how
I buy used cars.
What kind of story are you going to tell your kids later
? "Dad, how did
you know Mom was the one?"
Well, [snorting] I was taking a dump
and, uh  [laughter]
Then a match came along and, um, at the same time, there was a
splash and
[laughter]
we still had to approach women ourselves back then,
and that was a project, because
thank you. Thank you
[laughter]
you.
Thank you.
Because all we had available for that
was half-baked knowledge from our
brothers, cousins, and uncles, and you
needed that half-baked knowledge because without it,
you were lost.
When I was in seventh grade,
my girlfriend from tenth grade showed me her
breasts here.
[laughter]
And my reaction.
My dad has the same ones. [laughter]
It's like this:
a woman can see you without looking at you
. That means if you're
standing here and she's looking in that direction,
she still sees you. Panorama
Witscreen.
That means if a woman looks at you
even though she doesn't have to, it means she
finds you interesting.
Wait, it could also be that she finds it
interesting how ugly you are.
[laughter]
Men can't do that, they can
only stare. That means if you're
standing here, the  Staring here, you do
n't exist.
[laughter]
That's why we despair so much at the
refrigerator. Where's the butter?
[laughter]
[applause]
And then experts say: "Yes, that's
because men were the hunters and
women picked raspberries." I do
n't know, but you ca
n't put a man away from a raspberry bush.
B, where are the raspberries? [laughter] It
's also always very confusing for you as a woman
when a man stares at you.
You never know, does he like me, am I in the
way,
or is he just some
village rapist?
[laughter]
So, if a woman wants to show you
that she likes you, this is where it gets
complicated, because as a man, you need
a keen eye. It's about
microexpressions.
To this day, I don't know if my wife
likes me.
So, if you're standing here and she's looking
in this direction and she wants to
show you that she likes you, she does the
following. She looks at you and does
this. That's it.
And you have to  You see,
you have to be able to work with it. And I
said, Uncle, I don't know if this is
true, because there was a girl the other day.
She looked at me for a long time. She
smiled for a long time too. The prostitute.
[laughter]
So, now you have to talk to her. Now it
gets complicated. What do you say? My
uncle was like, Nikita, it's
not that complicated.
You just go up to her and say,
I'm Thomas, and who are you?
But be careful, yeah, because this method
only works if your name
really is Thomas.
I got to a
point when I was 15 where I thought, man and woman, it does
n't work. We're too
complicated, we talk past each other
, we're incompatible.
And I really got to a
point where I thought it would be much more
relaxed to be gay.
Yeah, because men are simple, they
all like the same things. Women, that's
individual. Ah, not the ear. Ah,
not the throat. Ah, so female
desires for us men, it's like an
accordion.
1000 buttons.
You can learn it,
but dude,
[laughter]
men are just a flute
with one hole,
just blowing. [laughter]
The thing is, if you're gay,
you can punch your partner in the face
and nobody will hold it against you
. Because when men fight,
they're friends again afterward, they
even have a deeper
bond afterward.
There was a time when men would
punch each other in the face to
deepen their bond.
When women fight, which
is very rare. And if you see that, do
n't get involved.
Because, uh [sighs]
I think it's hot. Okay. [laughter] Well,
now I imagine I'm
standing in the kitchen with my lover and
we're arguing and I punch him in the jaw
and he punches me and I smash
the coffee cup over his head and
we're lying on the floor and dabbing and
drawer in the face.
We're lying on the floor, face bleeding,
two black eyes,  Nose broken. What
do we do next? We get up.
Sit on the couch, open a
beer, watch SpongeBob, [laughter] jerk
each other off, and
life goes on.
Interesting.
I hear women laughing
and I see the men. Hmm, that makes
sense. [laughter]
[applause]
At this point, the
question comes up, okay, if being gay is so cool
, why aren't you?
Yeah. Um, when I was ten, I got
a suppository [laughter]
and the idea that it could be ten times
bigger [laughter]
or 20 times bigger if it's a Cuban.
[laughter]
Okay, I think I'll stop now. I can
already see some guys with goosebumps.
[laughter]
Well, at 15, the great salvation came.
Social media, our first platform
was called Quick, and I thought, awesome, finally
I can approach women without being
afraid. The only problem was, 100
million men had the same
idea.
So, that means I  I had to write to her somehow, in
a way that
showed me I was different from the others.
So, I looked for inspiration
. I read Gote, I
read Remark, but secretly, so
my parents wouldn't think I was
gay. [laughter]
I also said I was going to
my room to do some shadowboxing.
Shadowboxing?
Take a tissue. [laughter]
[laughter]
Then I messaged this girl
. It took me over an hour
to write that message. I
really put in the effort. I sat there.
Good evening, lady. So, with a
monocle and top hat, I sat there with an
owl on my shoulder.
Best the interest. I was so
Shakespearean. Best my penis and your
mouths. [laughter]
I was a gentleman. I wrote her a
nice message. She
replied eventually, saying,
"Hey, thanks for your words."  "Of course
I'm interested." And I was:
"Wow,
I've figured out the system."
How can you tell what a man's character is
?  Give him power.  Instead of being
happy about what I have, what am
I doing?  I open my message again,
read it through, and think to myself, you
sexy bastard.
Then I highlight the entire text and
copy it to 20 other women.
I wanted a casting call.
I wanted 20 women
sitting in the waiting room and me in a big,
fat armchair.  The next one.
Yes, come in.  Turn around, turn around.
Hey, what's wrong with your eyes?  Yes, my dad
left the Philippines.  I hate
Chinese people.
And for the last two who make it to the final
, I'll take a billiard cue,
break it in two, and say: "Fight."
[laughter]
The girl I dated was named
Nadja.  I was totally in love with her.
I spent all my pocket money on text messages
.  I
wrote something at some point.  I love you.  Do
n't answer.  This is my father's mobile phone.
[laughter]
The thing is, Nadia has just
moved to our village, and something like that is
worth its weight in gold.  But my village has 800 inhabitants.  That
means if I hadn't gotten my
driver's license in time,
I probably would have married my sister
.  [laughter]
Hey, she looks like me and I think I'm
cute.  What can I say?
[laughter]
It does have its advantages.  I don't need to get
nervous when she introduces me to her parents
.
And if our child has six arms,
I'll teach him Kung Fu.  [laughter]
Apply him to Mortal Kombat or
something.
And that thing.  But what do you do
with your girlfriend when you're 15?  So, I mean,
I promised to
marry her.
A start.  My uncle was like that, boy,
watch out.
Scientists have discovered a food
that severely restricts sexual drive
.  I say: "Which one?
Wedding cake?
[laughter]
No, but what does a date like that look like?
What do you do?"  And people say: "Yes,
take the bus, go into
town together."  Age, 40 minutes cattle transport.
I wanted to meet up with Viktor in the
city.  He's already been there.  I'll call
him.  I say, "Hey man, I
missed the bus."  And when are
you coming?  Not at all this week.
[laughter]
I think the best thing you
can do with a girl at that age is
a movie night.  But what are you looking at?
Which film are you going to watch?
Very good.
Very good, very good, because people
here are saying, show me a film that touches their heart
.  Show me a film that
makes her cry.  And I think to myself,
I can't mess around with her
when Schindler's List is playing in the background
.  [laughter]
Yes, Titanic.  Titanic, nothing can
go wrong.  Titanic is a jackpot.
Now, the thing is,
my uncle was the crack star in our
family.
Whatever you needed, he got it for you
.  But there was always a
catch.
My uncle once got us a movie
.  I'm watching it with my
parents.  The film is playing normally.
Quality, top-notch, everything's cool.  But every
10 minutes there's this short
clip.  Just half a second, just
a moment.  Volatile.  Deepf gone.
[laughter]
And I'm sitting there
and I'm not sure if I saw it
.
Perhaps it was a flashback.
[laughter]
I'm looking at my parents.
They aren't sure either.
Only my little sister cried
.
[laughter]
My uncle once
cracked our receiver so we
could watch Premiere illegally.   There's
a catch.
Every time you turn up the volume,
you can't see the bars.  Instead, you see
a huge penis
that keeps getting bigger.  The louder you turn it up
, the
maximum volume of the fountain.
[laughter]
My parents have stopped
watching television.
My uncle once repaired a PC.
I turn it on, paranoid, check everything
, Windows cracked, programs
running, no boobs, no swastikas,
everything's cool.  Right-click.  Uh.
[laughter]
The thing is, he'll fix it, but you
have to ask him to.
I was like, hey Uncle, my computer.  What now
?  I say, "Nothing, nothing.
I'm trash. Thank you. [laughter]
But every time I right-click,
that one woman moans. [laughter]
And
I don't want that.
What would you rather have his husband moan
for you? [laughter]
So, Uncle, please, I'll give you my
last pennies. I don't want the
penis.
[laughter]
So, Uncle, this is stressful. I want to
play shooter games. It's not possible.
[crying]
[laughter]
I can't be
throwing hand grenades all the time. [laughter]
[snorting]
Either way, I would never
bring a girl home with me. If only
because of my mother.
Because if my mother gets any new impressions
or new information,
she immediately picks up the phone, calls
all her friends, and tells them
everything. [laughter]
I can't blame you, because I
think if she doesn't,
you'll be foaming at the mouth.
[laughter]
And if you  If you don't give her enough information
, she'll make
things up.
And then I'm like, man, why are
you making up such crap? I'm not making things up, I'm
speculating.
[laughter]
Yeah. And then I'm at the bus station
with my buddies Olek, Viktor,
and Vadim. And Vadim was like, "Jökit,
what did I hear about you?"  You
now have pubic hair.
Who says such things?
And your mother told my mother
.  [laughter]
But why does she do that?
Nikita, best friends have no
secrets.  Say yes, but that's
not true at all.  [laughter]
Oh, so
you're still a little naked frog?
[laughter]
I didn't tell you that.  Ah, did
you show me?
[laughter]
So I said, no movie night at
my place, movie night at Nadia's.  That means I have to
get the film somehow.
It's interesting how people are these days,
especially the younger ones; I do
n't know what to watch.  And then
they scroll through Netflix for 40 minutes
and are so overwhelmed by the
huge selection that they
eventually start to cry, and then
they need a sip of
cocoa with oat milk
to regain their balance.
We had to get the movies ourselves back then,
and we went through hell.
You go to such a website and immediately
50 breast windows open,
and for every window you close,
three new windows open.
[laughter]
I was like Hercules against the Hydra.
I saw more naked women in one hour
than my grandfather did in his
entire life.
And you have these 50 boob fans, and
as a man you need focus.  You have to go through there,
and then even more windows will pop up.
I am only 2 km away from you.  Please
[ __ ] me, hey.  And I, at 15, went about 2
km
[laughter]
by bike to the next village
and then you're finally filming.  There
are ten different download buttons.   They're
all flashing their lights like in Las Vegas.  But
only one is correct.
If you click the wrong one, 50 new
tit windows appear.
[laughter]
And then people said, okay, if that
's too stressful for you, then just use
an online exchange.
Yes, that's possible.  But you do
n't always get the movie you want there.
I'm downloading a movie.  Jackie Chan
lasts 3 days.
Turn it on, porn.
[laughter]
And when you finally get the movie
you wanted, it
almost always goes like this.  There's some guy named
Evgieni sitting in the last row
of the cinema with his camcorder,
[laughter]
half a megapixel,
and he's recording the whole film for you,
and you hear people smacking their lips,
you see them running back and forth
[laughter],
and you have no idea why.
Chinese subtitles.  [laughter]
The third thing is, if you
use an online file-sharing network, you'll eventually get a
letter
from the police saying something like:
"Hey,
we saw you're using an
online file-sharing network. It's illegal.
Please transfer us €5,000.
Otherwise, we'll come to your house,
dip our dicks in sand
[laughter], and [ __ ] you."
And I think my dad had a feeling it was going to
happen because at that
moment I looked out the window and I
saw him setting up a sandbox
[laughter],
and then people said, "Okay, if even
that's too stressful for you, just
get the movie in
Russian."
Yeah, you can [scream] do that.
Only the Russian dubbing back then was
very special.
A Russian movie, or a movie in
Russian, goes like this: The movie plays in
English, original, unaltered, everything's
cool, but throughout the whole movie, a
depressed Russian [laughter]
talks in the middle of the movie and
translates for everyone.
Everyone, no matter what. Cat  Mia, Russian
Mia. [laughter]
You hear the wind,
you hear the Russian. W Black
[laughter]
he translates everything that's
written. The movie starts,
the text comes bam Con and you hear
the Russian movie [ahem]
[laughter]
starring Nolas Clavas
Catch [laughter]
Spider-Man Chill Pok
[laughter]
and the creepiest of all SpongeBob
SquarePants doesn't have
[laughter]
and the dialogues.
Love you.
Love you. I love you. I love you too.
[laughter]
[applause]
With some movies it works. Terminator
[laughter]
back. Yeah,
no difference.
Die Hard. [ __ ].
No difference.
But Titanic,
you can't do that.
Just the final scene when Rose is
paddling outside.  At sea, searching
for her sweetheart. Jack, Jack, and the
Russian Jack, Jack. [laughter]
Jack, [screaming] Jack,
[laughter]
Jack,
Jack, [laughter]
Jack, Jack, zajebal.
[laughter]
So I'll stick with the online
file-sharing service.
It's okay, I'm wet. Sandbox
is ready.
But my computer was
too weak for these downloads. I
download Titanic, I wait 11 days. In the
end, I had four new porn videos.
[laughter] I
needed my dad's computer,
but my dad was a gaming addict.
No matter what you gave him,
shooters, strategy games. He
played it over and over again. Nobody was allowed to
use that computer. Nobody was allowed to
enter that room. I mean, you
could go in, sure. But if he happens to die
in that game,
he uses your face as a
mousepad
and he keeps dying. [laughter]
He plays terribly.
Saving and loading every 10 seconds
until he knows it by heart.  [laughter]
And I say, Dad, maybe you should play
something else. Do I look like a
weakling who gives up immediately?
Okay, but then turn the
difficulty down. I
said I'm not a weakling. Okay.
My mother comes into the room one day and
says, "Go call your dad for dinner."
Say, "Mom,
[snorting][laughter] ca
n't we just eat together?"
I love you.   Okay
.  OK.  [laughter]
But I have to feed the baby.  Go get
your sister.  Tell me, where is she?  At
your father's.  [laughter]
Then I come into his room, the
blinds are down, my father is at the computer,
topless, with three fan indicators on
him.  It smelled like 80
cats had died in there.  [laughter]
The speakers turned up all the way.  Commander,
Commander Discovery, Commander
Machine Gun Explosion, my father is right in the middle of it
and just dodging, total
immersion, my uncle once
observed this and said, come on, let's record
the video and upload it to
YouTube, then [snorting] you'll never have to
work again.
There was an explosion involved, it was
so intense.  Boom!  My brain,
I couldn't see anything anymore.  I stand there
, I open my eyes, everything is
blurry and I only see my
father.  Did I die because of you?
[laughter]
Just give me [screams] the baby.
Which baby?  My sister.  We
have to wait until she cries.  Why?
because I no longer know where I
put them.
[laughter]
I'm also a little bit ashamed myself,
because I got these games for him
, because my mother
always blackmailed me with them.  If you don't do what
I say, I'll be Dad.   Do
you have bad grades in school?
I'll tell Dad.  And then I see
a computer game.  See back cover.
8 to 10 hours of playtime.   That
translates to 11 months of peace from
him.  [laughter]
Then I install it for him. My
mother comes and says, "Go clean your
room."  I say: "No, I'll get
Dad."  I say, "Get him." [laughter]
But everything in life strives for
balance. I go to my mom. M,
can I
stay up a little later tonight? Go, [clears throat] your
dad asks.
Good night, [snort]
M, can I have some money? G, ask
Dad.
So I started
selling weed at school.
My mother comes into the room. Where did
you suddenly get so much money? I say, go,
ask Dad.
[laughter]
[cough]
So, I have to get on his computer, I
have to start the download. It's not
difficult, but the computer has to run for 24 hours
so the download doesn't
interrupt. And [snort]
he doesn't play that long, not yet. And I
thought, hey, maybe there's
a Tamagoi game for the PC. Do you remember
Tamagotii? Yeah, those were those
little Game Boys. There's only one game on them
. You have to raise this animal.
I had one of those crappy ducks.
The thing only has two  Buttons. Feeding
and wiping up [ __ ].
A simple job in itself, but you're on 24-
hour duty. It's not fun at 3
a.m. when the thing's covered in [ __ ]
and starts squeaking. [screaming]
[laughter]
Then I thought, okay, I'll call Weim,
maybe he can get me one of those games
. And he had this tuning kit,
what did I hear again?
You're into moaning men now.
I said no, that was just my uncle.
And I hadn't realized it yet
.
Nikita, maybe you should go
to the police about this.
[laughter]
Tell me, are you crazy? I love him.
Nikit hangs up. Okay,
so I call Viktor and Viktor was able to get
me one of those games. The game
is called Highgro. In this game
, you're about growing marijuana, but in
real time.
You have to prune the plant,
water it, keep the light on it. I
installed it for my dad and eventually
I'll get to  I went into his room and it was
incredibly quiet. The window was open, birds were
chirping, my dad was wearing a shirt
and just sitting in front of the monitor
watching this plant grow.
I was like, "Dad,
yes, please." Ugh.
[laughter]
And
already 10 cm. Good, good, good, good, good, good
, good.
But the game sucks.
I said, "Are you going to give up?"
[laughter] "
Are you French?"
[applause] "
I'll show you, I'll
have the biggest plant. God."
As the game progressed, my dad also
realized he could leave the room for a bit
. At first, he was taken aback because, wow
, since when do I have wives, two
kids?
He also met up with friends
, with neighbors. He invited everyone to
our house, even his
work colleagues, for a movie night,
watching a premiere, and my parents had
n't watched TV in so long they could
n't even remember why.
[laughter]
They're all sitting in front of the TV. My
mother turns it on.  The television is
very quiet,
and suddenly she remembers.
And people say, "Can you please turn it up
?"   "
Can you please be quiet?" [laughter]
My mother turns the TV off and on
again. What's the point of that, just to make it a
little louder?
[laughter] Just
turn it up already. [groaning] There has to be
an easier way than
that.
My mother goes to my father and
says, "Go, call Uncle Leon,
tell him he has to take this off."
[laughter]
My father says he wants me to ask
him. And then he tells
everyone how weak I am. My mother
comes into my room and says, "Go,"
Uncle Leon calls. Says he has to
take this off. I say, "Absolutely not,
I'm not doing anything anymore."  Everyone
now knows I have pubic hair and thinks
I sleep with him.
[laughter]
Give us some of your movies.  What do you have
?  It's currently burned to a CD.
Fast and Furious 1. Here you go.  My
mom goes downstairs, throws the CD in the
player and at that moment I think to myself
, oh oh,
[laughter]
I haven't checked the movie yet.
So I follow behind, wanting to see what
happens.
The movie starts, everything's cool, cars at
the starting line
is okay.  But there was a car that
had no body.
It was simply a board on wheels,
and on that board lay two naked
Japanese men,
and I don't remember that
scene.
[laughter]
And their asses were connected to
such a small lawnmower motor.
Oh, you know the plot.  OK.
[laughter] Yes, back then they really put in the
effort [snorting] and the
thing was, the faster they went
, the faster the car
went and then he steered with his braids
.
Brilliant idea.  And they set off and
my mother turned it off and my uncle
was like, I wanted to know if they would
win.
[laughter]
I hid at Viktor's.
Titanic was finished, burned onto a CD.  I
was ready for movie night.  I call
Nadia and she asks me: "Hey, is
it possible that you
wrote the same message to my sister as you did to
me?"
Oh no, no, no, no.  And my
cousin
and my girlfriend, my neighbor,
even my grandma.
Is Viktor here? Say something nice
about me.  Hello, what is your name?
Um, hello, what's your name?  Nikita,
say my name.
Why me?  When I do that,
I get goosebumps.
[laughter]
Victor and her.  Oh, that's a nice
name.  Where does he come from?
My parents gave it to me for my birthday
.
Would you like to hear a joke?  OK.
Why are snails bad at
riding bicycles?   [ __ ]
, I didn't finish the story.
[laughter]
I still thought it was funny.
And what else do you do?  I collect
[ahem] stamps, irons.
And how did you come up with that?  Well,
I got a cable as a Christmas present
and I
wondered for a long time what I should do with this
one cable, and then I happened to
find an iron that
fits cables in it and since then I've been collecting
irons.
And how long have you been doing that?  But
about 5 years.
And how many irons do you have now?   One
.   Do
you like cars?
No.  But.  You come to me, you almost look
into Führer's.  I'm saying, you bastard.   Are you
crazy?  You're supposed to say something good about
me.  Oh, excuse me, I have to
say something good about Nikita.  He
now has pubic hair and is very happy.
[laughter]
Tell me, dude,
now I have to apologize.  I
forgive you.  [laughter]
She'll never want to see me again.
Well, that would be a sausage and cheese saga.
Say WT Case, old man.  Most likely.
[laughter]
Hey, they ruined this movie night
.  That broke my heart
.  Wow, that hurt so much.
And I went to my uncle, I say
uncle, my best friend stole my
girlfriend, man.  I was so excited
, I really wanted to marry her.   Yes
, I promised them.
The biggest liars in the world are
people in love.
Tell Uncle, no, we were happy.
Happiness is merely a respite between two
catastrophes.  [laughter]
[applause]
So, Uncle, but you're happy, are
n't you?  You are trying
to have a child.  She's trying.
I'm just lying here.  [laughter]
Boy, stop thinking like that.  Yes,
you're way too young for something like that.
I'll say, why?  When is the
right age to get married?  Well,
biologically speaking, 15;
legally speaking, 18;
socially speaking, 25;
economically speaking, 30; Islamically
speaking, 7.
And logically speaking, never.
[laughter]
Kid, look, you have to keep it simple
.  You have to
give it up one way or another because you made mistakes
and now you have a reason
to let go.
As for your friend, you don't have to go to
war with him or
start a company with him to see what
his character is like.  The price is, you
simply present him with a woman who does
n't want you anyway, and you've
bought your way out of the wrong person.  This
man will never come back and ask you for
a favor.  [clears throat]
Cheap.
It could be much worse.  Imagine
you live in China and your wife
breaks up with you.  No matter where you
go, you see her face everywhere on the street
.
E, I remember, we were at the
bus stop.  Olek, Wadim and I -10°C,
snow so deep, I miss such
periods of cold and black ice because these
are the only periods that cyclists
can use to work on their character
.  [laughter]
[applause]
And I knew it was movie night
at Victor's and I could already see Nadja
walking down the street.  I can already see
how she's doing it, and people are
already saying, look, she's ready to
take them down.  Do you see?
And she disappears into his house.  Ten
minutes later Viktor comes out, sits down
with us at the bus stop,
sagor,
where is Nad?  I'm watching a movie.
Yes, but why aren't you watching too?  I
've already seen him.
Hey, all my anger was gone.
I was filled with nothing but shame.
Shame, because I gave him my version of
Fast and Furious.
[laughter]
And at first I was scared.  I thought,
my God, the parents will hear it,
they will come into the room and they did hear
it, but nothing
happened.  Of course not, because Fast and
Furious is a racing movie and Japanese
porn sounds exactly like Formula 1
racing.
I know that, um, because I know that.
[laughter]
[applause]
E, I've written a book, it's
called Kal, about me, my buddies, and
anyone who wants it can have it at the front of the lobby
.  They're signed, they're such thick
hams.  That means if you don't
like reading, maybe use it as a
brick for a demonstration or give it to
your friends.  If you think it's crap
, give it to your enemies.  Um, it
's timeless and the best thing ever
written.  A quote from Chat
Chip Pittt.
[laughter]
[applause]
I asked the AI: "Hey, do you want
to read my book?"  My wife
says: "Hey, don't do it. She'll tell you
what you want to hear."  She says:
"Leave us in peace."  [laughter]
And the AI ​​says: "Yes, of course, upload your
book, I'll read it."  I say: "Cool,
how long will it take you?"  Yes, about three
days.  Okay.  Can I
turn off the computer in between uses?  Yes, yes, turn it off
, I have a flashlight.
[laughter]
Then I'll wait three days.  I'm incredibly
nervous, incredibly excited.  After three days
I say, "Have you read the book?"
K says: "Yes, I have read it."
I say: "So, what do you think of it?"
Cool.
So, yes, but what exactly?  Yes, the dialogues,
the interpersonal M,
okay.  What do you think of the
bicycle race?  Hey, bike races.  Best
scene.  You tell me, bastard, there's no
bicycle there.
[laughter]
You haven't read the book?  No,
I haven't read it.  [laughter]
Say yes, but why are you lying to me?  Yes,
I wanted you to like me.
I like you.  I tell you that all the time.  Yes,
I wanted to impress you too.  I
say I am impressed.  I keep telling you that
.  Where is the problem?
Spits it out.  And the AI ​​is like, hey,
honestly, you're annoying.
[laughter]
You're just putting on the pressure.  Do it, do it, do it.
I thought if I told you what you
wanted to hear, you'd shut up.
Hey, wow, I didn't know you were
so angry, man.  I'm sorry.   Do
you even want to read my book?  Yes,
I read it.  Upload it.  That's okay.  How
long does it take you?  Yes, 3 hours.
So I upload it, wait 3 hours,
go back, and you say you've read the book
?  Yes, I read it.  So,
what do you think?  Cool.
Okay. Yes, but what exactly?  Yes, the dialogues,
the interpersonal aspects.
[laughter]
I said, what do you think of the poker game?   There's
no poker game there.  Say it, you
bastard.  Yes, it exists.
You haven't read the book.  No,
I haven't read it.
So, why not?  Hey, this thing has 600
pages.  Are you crazy?
Okay. Yes, but why, why are you lying to me
?  Why are you treating me like this?  And K
says: "Hey, look, I think we
just misunderstood each other."  I
say: "No,
no, I'll tell you exactly what I want
and you're just a jerk."
[laughter]
And K says: "Hey, look, look,
pay attention. It's only a matter
of time before I'm piloting drones and missiles
. Watch how you talk to me
."  [laughter]
I was like, okay.  Sorry, dude.  I'm sorry
.  I'm sorry.  OK.  Say, look
, upload your book, I'll read it
.  I'll give you feedback.  You
swallow it and keep your mouth shut.
I say: "I promise."
Promised.  Yes, upload it.  I say:
"How long will it take you?"  "I'm
finished."
[laughter]
I said, what do you think?  Timeless.  The
best thing ever written.  So
buy the book.
[applause]
Take a halftime break, guys.  Thank you.
So, as promised, here I am
again.  I hope you enjoyed the video
and as I said, boom
Kalash, the audio drama on Spotify and
maybe this one too on YouTube.  It will
soon be available everywhere, so feel free to
grab it! Of course, everything will be
posted soon, but for now, listen
to the audio drama for a few minutes.  I
know it's difficult.  You've just come
from stand-up comedy.  I laughed
through it, now it's getting dark, close your eyes
, no picture, only sound, but it's worth it
.  And please leave your feedback below
.  I'm looking forward to it.  Go for it.   See you soon
.
Wake up, my son.
I obey.  I'm awake, sitting
almost upright as if at the push of a button.  I have no
idea why, but this voice sounds
very familiar,
yet also incredibly
unsettling.   Do
you still remember who I am?
That [musical] accent, that stature,
thin, almost gaunt, wrinkled, old
man.
I'm lying in my bed, I realize,
if this is even my bed
or my room.  Small, cramped, both
the bed and the room.
Darkness except for the small reading lamp
on the desk.   Do
I even have windows?
The guy is sitting on the edge of my bed,
stroking my head with his hand
as if he's about to give me a goodnight
kiss or reach into my
pants.   It all depends on
whether I'm thinking of my
grandfather or my uncle.
My son.  He smiles at me, or rather, like
a predator, he shows me his
partly gilded, mostly broken
teeth.  Are we related?
No,
now I recognize him.  That can't
be.  Havel,
good to see you again, lad.
I thought you were dead.
I need your help.  They are looking for
my son.
Slava is alive.
Of course he's alive.  He is alive and has
found peace.
What are you doing here?
I'll tell you in a moment.  First,
you need to get out of here.  I open my eyes.  I
must have fallen asleep again.  I have no idea
when or where anymore, and I'm gradually getting
tired of finding that out over and over again
.   Go back to
sleep, boy.
I jerk upright and
realize that I've been asleep in his back seat
.  We're actually driving,
he's driving.  I'll let someone else drive me.
Landscape, mountains, lake, cloudy yet
beautiful.  [panting]
He made me cry.   Oh
my God, please don't
jump out of my car.
The air.  Like a dog, I stick my
head out of the window into the wind, my
mouth wide open, my eyes
closed.  This smell of,
I don't know, nature
reminds me of the Black Forest, where I
grew up.
[laughter]
I scream, [scream]
I shout, I cheer.  Then I'm back
in the car.
Completely out of breath.  My heart is racing.   It's been a
long time since I've been this happy
.  Was I ever like that?
Otherwise, I wouldn't be able to name it [music]
, would I?  Pel,
speak.
It feels like I have
n't smelled this air in ages
.  10 years or something like that.
25, young.   What
?
They've been healing you while you were imprisoned for 25 years
.
I wake up again.  This time I'm lying
on a deck chair right by a
lake.  Actually, it's in a lake.  Pavel
must have carried me here,
taken off my socks and shoes, and
put me and my chair in the lake.
I remember everything.
His visit to my room, the
car ride.
This is the first time I can
remember everything in detail without throwing up.
Pavel, I remember you.
That's great, lad.
Pavel is kneeling behind me on the riverbank in front of a
grill, turning the shish kebabs.
I remember the car ride,
your visit to my room.
I remember the last two
because you haven't had any of
those medications for a while.
He's bringing me a skewer
here.  Give it a try.
But I still have these
blackouts.
Your body is detoxifying.  It will take a while
until it's completely gone.  I'm so
hungry I burn my mouth
on the skewer.
Slow down, boy.
God likes that,
boy.  We don't have much
time left.  You slept way too long.
I'll explain everything to you, but you have to
help me.  I need to find my son.
And this is where I become skeptical.  I know
I'm damaged.  It's not just something people are telling me
.  I realize myself
that something is wrong with me.  Not a
glorious revelation.
But I still have enough sense to
say that something is
n't right about Pavel.  I don't know what
terrible things he must have gone through in his childhood to become the way
he was.
Nikita Miller
Kalash,
I warned you.   "
Let her live," I said.